THALES 姜泰



PROFILE

With 20 years of **development** experience, including 15 years in **management** and 5 years in **artificial intelligence**, I have a deep passion for research and development and am constantly keeping up with the latest developments in the industry. I possess strong research abilities and have successfully implemented multiple research papers. As a manager, I have led teams of over 100 people and have extensive experience in team management.

CONTACT DETAILS

@ jiangtai20@mails.ucas.ac.cn

+86 138 1093 5087

⊠ 1st Xi'erqi road, Haidian, Beijing

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Year of birth: 1981 Family: Married with dependent Languages: English, Chinese (native)

SKILLS

- Python, C++, SQL, DevOps
- TypeScript, WebGl, Node.js
- Blockchain, Smart Contract, DAO
- Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Reinforcement Learning
- Communication and team collaboration

EXPERIENCE

ARCHITECTURE at Institute of Automation, Chinese Academy of Sciences. **2019.7–pres.**

⋄ Building Framework, Project Management, Data Analysis, Data Mining. Blockchain, DAO, Smart Contact, Web3.o, Recursive Inscriptions. Reinforcement Learning, Route Plan, Simulation, Engineering Optimization. Multi-Object Detection, Augmented Reality, 3D Reconstriction.

ARCHITECTURE at JD.com, inc.

2018.4-2019.7

Building Software or Web, Construct Framework, Optimization.

Developed an auction system and a recycling system.

Created a common component library.

Providing efficient and user-friendly solutions for the company's operations. Improving development efficiency and consistency across projects.

Successfully managed a team of over 100 people

Ensuring effective communication and coordination for project delivery.

CTO at Vogso Ltd. (Hong Kong).

2010.8-2018.3

Building Web and Game, Construct Framework, Assign Management.
Stablished and managed a team for the development and optimization
Led the technical selection, architecture design, and development of the system.

Expanded the company's presence by opening a new branch office. Managed the team's performance and ensured timely delivery of high-quality products.

ENGINEERING at Our Palm inc.

2008.3-2010.7

Building Game, Developing, Database, Optimization.

Develop real-time combat system.

Game in a daily active user count of over 10,000.

EDITOR at Xinhua Computer College.

2004.4-2008.3

Teach web knowledge.

EDUCATION

PH.D. DEGREE WITH THE INSTITUTE OF SYSTEM ENGINEERING. Intelligent Science and Systems. *Macau University of Science and Technology*. **2023–pres**

- ♦ Thesis title: Journal DAO: User-Incentivized Autonomous Decentralized Scientific Publishing in Web3.
- ♦ Decentralized autonomous organizations, Blockchain, Web3.0, DeFi, DeSci.

MASTER OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION. Artificial Intelligence and Application. *University of Chinese Academy of Sciences.* **2020–2022**

- ♦ Thesis title: Smart Resale Based on Multi-Object Detection and Augmented Reality.
- ♦ Machine Learning, Time Series, Multi-Object Detection, Augmented Reality, User Experience.

Computer Network. Xijing University.

2001-2004

⋄ Developing, Network, Framework.

HOBBIES

Sport: Badmnton, Sketing, Bowling, Archery.

Miscellaneous: Astronomy, Zoology, Consumer Psychology.